{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4889","name":"Top China One","address":"3157 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Cun Di Chen","licenseNumber":"078536","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.05672,42.34553","geojson":{"id":"4889","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.056717343,42.345525474]},"properties":{"name":"Top China One","owner":"Cun Di Chen","address":"3157 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"078536","establishmentid":"4889","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"6/2/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"51622555","name":"Empire","address":"3148 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"739","name":"Coalition on Temporary Shelter","address":"26 Peterboro St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"371","name":"Detroit #1 Coney Island","address":"3433 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5383","name":"New Order Coffee Roasters","address":"3100 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622588","name":"JJA Detroit LLC / DBA BakersField","address":"3100 Woodward Ave ","zipcode":"48201-34"},{"establishmentid":"5224","name":"Pho Lucky","address":"3111 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622670","name":"Second Best Bar","address":"42 E Watson St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51622556","name":"For The Love of Sugar","address":"100 Erskine St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"806","name":"King David Grand Lodge","address":"114 Erskine St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"808","name":"Detroit Urban League","address":"208 Mack Ave","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50332","inspectionDate":"2020-01-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-802.11","violationDescription":"(A) LINENS that do not come in direct contact with FOOD shall be laundered between operations if they become wet, sticky, or visibly soiled.   \r\n(B) Cloth gloves used as specified in ¶ 3-304.15(D) shall be laundered before being used with a different type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork or POULTRY.   \r\n(C) LINENS and napkins that are used as specified under § 3-304.13 and cloth napkins shall be laundered between each use.   \r\n(D) Wet wiping cloths shall be laundered daily.   \r\n(E) Dry wiping cloths shall be laundered as necessary to prevent contamination of FOOD and clean serving UTENSILS.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact linen(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not laundered when","subProblem":"Visibly soiled","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48461","inspectionDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"after other activities","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-07-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-802.11","violationDescription":"(A) LINENS that do not come in direct contact with FOOD shall be laundered between operations if they become wet, sticky, or visibly soiled.   \r\n(B) Cloth gloves used as specified in ¶ 3-304.15(D) shall be laundered before being used with a different type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork or POULTRY.   \r\n(C) LINENS and napkins that are used as specified under § 3-304.13 and cloth napkins shall be laundered between each use.   \r\n(D) Wet wiping cloths shall be laundered daily.   \r\n(E) Dry wiping cloths shall be laundered as necessary to prevent contamination of FOOD and clean serving UTENSILS.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact linen(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not laundered when","subProblem":"Visibly soiled","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"At least every 24 hours","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"NON FOOD CONTACT SURFACES","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44201","inspectionDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"REACH-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"KITCHEN","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep covered."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"REACH-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Back Room","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in protected manner."},{"violationCode":"4-901.11","violationDescription":"After cleaning and SANITIZING, EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS shall be air-dried or used after adequate draining.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment and utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored/stacked wet","subProblem":"","location":"DISH ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Completely air dry all items prior to storage/use."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-06-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."}]},{"inspectionid":"42623","inspectionDate":"2018-06-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"2-301.14","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall clean their hands and exposed portions of their arms as specified under § 2-301.12 immediately before engaging in FOOD preparation including working with exposed FOOD, clean EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES (P) and:\r\n(A)     After touching bare human body parts other than clean hands and clean, exposed portions of arms; (P)\r\n(B)     After using the toilet room; (P)\r\n(C)     After caring for or handling SERVICE ANIMALS or aquatic animals as specified in ¶ 2-403.11(B); (P).\r\n(D)     Except as specified in ¶ 2-401.11(B), after coughing, sneezing, using a handkerchief or disposable tissue, using tobacco, eating, or drinking; (P)\r\n(E)     After handling soiled EQUIPMENT or UTENSILS; (P)\r\n(F)     During FOOD preparation, as often as necessary to remove soil and contamination and to prevent cross contamination when changing tasks; (P)\r\n(G)     When switching between working with raw FOOD and working with READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(H)     Before donning gloves for working with FOOD; (P) and\r\n(I)      After engaging in other activities that contaminate the hands. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Employee(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Did not wash hands","subProblem":"after other activities","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Hands shall be washed with hot water and soap for at least 20 seconds after contamination."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-06-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"flies","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"insects","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"REACH-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"KITCHEN","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep covered."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not tight-fitting","subProblem":"","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"Screening","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."}]},{"inspectionid":"41103","inspectionDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"Cooler (top loader)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-06-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"Lights","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-06-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"40981","inspectionDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"Cooler (top loader)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"39459","inspectionDate":"2017-06-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"In the Cooler (top loader)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Raw ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"In the Cooler (top loader)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-06-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"In water less than 135 degrees f","location":"COOKING AREA","subLocation":"Next to the Rice cooker","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-06-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain water at 135 degrees F or greater."},{"violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Bulk food containers","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Food contact surfaces","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37559","inspectionDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2016-12-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"Lack of HAND WASHING","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"NON FOOD CONTACT SURFACES","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4889"}}